Guide to the James Hazen Hyde Collection of Allegorical Prints of the Four Continents ca. 1500-ca.1900 PR 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Allegorical, American and English
  - America (JHH# 126 / Enregistre# 1353), ca. 1799 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    18th Century English Etching, mezzotint, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: P. Stampa
  - America (JHH# 127 / Enregistre# 1354) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    Artist: Philip Dawe [?] Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Deputies from the four Quarters of the Globe (JHH# 338 / Enregistre# 1356) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    Artist: Dodd Printmaker: Pass Publisher:
  - Europe America (JHH# 2000 / Enregistre# 1357), ca. 1799 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: P. Gally
  - An Emblem of Europe (JHH# 2773 / Enregistre# 1358) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
  - An Emblem of Asia (JHH# 2774 / Enregistre# 1359) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
  - An Emblem of Africa (JHH# 2775 / Enregistre# 1360) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
  - An Emblem of America (JHH# 2776 / Enregistre# 1361) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
  - The four parts of the World (JHH# 3017 / Enregistre# 1363), 1814 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    19th Century English Mezzotint, etching
  - America (JHH# 3097 / Enregistre# 1364) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    19th Century English Mezzotinit
  - The Western Prospect of St. Pauls Church (JHH# 4217 / Enregistre# 1368) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    Artist: Lens Printmaker: H. Hulsbergh Publisher: Phil. Overton
  - Almighty God Hath Blesses Nelson with Victory (JHH# 5168 / Enregistre# 1369), 1805 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    19th Century English Etching, engraving, mezzotint, hand coloring
    Artist: J. Eckstein Printmaker: J.C. Stadler Publisher: R. Ackermanns
  - An Emblem of America (JHH# 5461 / Enregistre# 1370), 1800 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    19th Century English Mezzotint, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: P. Barnaschina
  - Britannia and the Tribute of Trade (JHH# 6115 / Enregistre# 1372), 1770 (Folder Portfolio 5A)
    Artist: A. Walker Printmaker: A. Walker Publisher:
  - Columbia Trading with all the World (JHH# 6116 / Enregistre# 1373) (Folder Portfolio 5A)
  - Asia (JHH# 1302 / Enregistre# 1374), 1870 (Folder Portfolio 5B)
    19th Century American Lithograph, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Currier and Ives
  - Africa (JHH# 3110 / Enregistre# 1379) (Folder Portfolio 5B)
    19th Century English Hard and soft ground etching, hand coloring
    Artist: Lloyd Printmaker: Lloyd Publisher:
  - Africa America (JHH# 3111 / Enregistre# 1380) (Folder Portfolio 5B)
  - Neptune introducing the Four Quarters of the World (JHH# 3125 / Enregistre# 1381), 1803 (Folder Portfolio 5B)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: I. Hinton
  - Emblematical Representation of Commerce and Plenty (JHH# 6100 / Enregistre# 1382) (Folder Portfolio 5B)
    19th Century English Photomechanical reproduction
  - America (JHH# 6137 / Enregistre# 1383) (Folder Portfolio 5B)
  - [Listing of English postal rates] (JHH# 7388 / Enregistre# 1384) (Folder Portfolio 5B)
    19th Century English Etching
    Artist: W. Mulready Printmaker: Publisher: John Thompson
- Series VIII: Allegorical, French
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 309 / Enregistre# 1385) (Folder Portfolio 6A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Berey
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 320 / Enregistre# 1386) (Folder Portfolio 6A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Daumont
  - Europe (JHH# 1102 / Enregistre# 1388), 1575 (Folder Portfolio 6A)
    16th Century French Etching
    Artist: Etienne Delaune Printmaker: Etienne Delaune Publisher:
  - Asie (JHH# 1103 / Enregistre# 1389), 1575 (Folder Portfolio 6A)
  - Africca [sic] (JHH# 1104 / Enregistre# 1390), 1575 (Folder Portfolio 6A)
  - Americca [sic] (JHH# 1105 / Enregistre# 1391), 1575 (Folder Portfolio 6A)
  - Asia Africa Europa America (JHH# 5034 / Enregistre# 1392), 1618 (Folder Portfolio 6A)
    Artist: L. Gaultier Printmaker: L. Gaultier Publisher:
  - Tympanistas, Tubicen, Americani (JHH# 137 / Enregistre# 1393) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    Artist: Francois Chauveau Printmaker: Francois Chauveau Publisher:
  - Mauri Simios portantes, Ursos ducentes (JHH# 138 / Enregistre# 1394) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Stipatores, Equus Ductitius, Agasones, Americani (JHH# 139 / Enregistre# 1395) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Castrorum Proefectus Americanus (JHH# 14 / Enregistre# 1397) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Armiger, Ephebus, Americani (JHH# 140 / Enregistre# 1396) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Americanorum Rex, Guisius (JHH# 142 / Enregistre# 1398) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 152 / Enregistre# 1399) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    Artist: Pierre Gallays Printmaker: Pierre Gallays Publisher:
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 351 / Enregistre# 1400) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    Artist: Le Brun? Printmaker: F. de Wit Publisher:
  - L'Europe (JHH# 865 / Enregistre# 1401) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    Artist: Nicolas Arnoult Printmaker: Publisher: Nicolas Arnoult
  - L'Asie (JHH# 866 / Enregistre# 1402) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 867 / Enregistre# 1403) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - La Merique (JHH# 868 / Enregistre# 1404) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Europa (JHH# 1327 / Enregistre# 1405) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    17th Century French Etching, hand coloring
    Artist: Vignon Printmaker: H.D. Publisher: Firens
  - Asia (JHH# 1328 / Enregistre# 1406) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Africa (JHH# 1329 / Enregistre# 1407) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - America (JHH# 1330 / Enregistre# 1408) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Les differentes Nations de l'Europe (JHH# 1465 / Enregistre# 1409), 1720 (Folder Portfolio 6B)
    Artist: Charles Le Brun Printmaker: Louis Surugue Publisher: Louis Surugue
  - Les differentes Nations de l'Asie (JHH# 1466 / Enregistre# 1410), 1720 (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Les differentes Nations de l'Afrique (JHH# 1467 / Enregistre# 1411), 1720 (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - Les differentes Nations de l'Amerique (JHH# 1468 / Enregistre# 1412), 1720 (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1667 / Enregistre# 1417) (Folder Portfolio 6B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 2890 / Enregistre# 1418) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: H. Bonnart
  - L'Asie (JHH# 2891 / Enregistre# 1419) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Henri Bonnart
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 2892 / Enregistre# 1420) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 2893 / Enregistre# 1421) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 2894 / Enregistre# 1422) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Maurice
  - L'Asie (JHH# 2895 / Enregistre# 1423) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 2896 / Enregistre# 1424) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - Europe (JHH# 3199 / Enregistre# 1425) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Bernard Picart Publisher: Bernard Picart
  - Asie (JHH# 3200 / Enregistre# 1426) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - Afrique (JHH# 3201 / Enregistre# 1427) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - Amerique (JHH# 3202 / Enregistre# 1428) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 3270 / Enregistre# 1429) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Berey Publisher: Berey
  - L'Asie (JHH# 3271 / Enregistre# 1430) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 3272 / Enregistre# 1431) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3273 / Enregistre# 1432) (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 3666 / Enregistre# 1433), 1696 (Folder Portfolio 6C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Henri Bonnart Publisher: Coq
  - L'Asie (JHH# 3667 / Enregistre# 1434), 1696 (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 3668 / Enregistre# 1435), 1696 (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3669 / Enregistre# 1436), 1696 (Folder Portfolio 6C)
  - Europa (JHH# 3740 / Enregistre# 1437) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: DuBois
  - Asia (JHH# 3741 / Enregistre# 1438) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - Africa (JHH# 3742 / Enregistre# 1439) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - America (JHH# 3743 / Enregistre# 1440) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - America (JHH# 4689 / Enregistre# 1441), 1700 (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    17th Century French Stipple
  - Europa (JHH# 5088 / Enregistre# 1442) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Aveline Printmaker: Publisher: J.A. Pfeffel
  - Asia (JHH# 5089 / Enregistre# 1443) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - Africa Africa (JHH# 5090 / Enregistre# 1444) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - America (JHH# 5091 / Enregistre# 1445) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 6265 / Enregistre# 1446) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Printmaker: Pierre Gallays Publisher:
  - Europa (JHH# 6459 / Enregistre# 1447) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    17th Century Italian? Etching
    Artist: Printmaker: Johan Jakob Thourneyser Publisher: Johan Jakob Thourneyser
  - Asia (JHH# 6460 / Enregistre# 1448) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Bassano? Printmaker: Johan Jakob Thourneyser Publisher: Johan Jakob Thourneyser
  - Asia (JHH# 6461 / Enregistre# 1449) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - America (JHH# 6462 / Enregistre# 1450) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - Asia (JHH# 6520 / Enregistre# 1451) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Charles Le Brun Printmaker: Aegid. Rousselet Publisher: Jean Le Blond
  - [Four Continents] (JHH# 7216 / Enregistre# 1452) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - [Four Corners of the Globe United under the Bourbo (JHH# 7549 / Enregistre# 1453) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
    Artist: Printmaker: Trouvain Publisher:
  - La Royale famille de Bourbon (JHH# 7711 / Enregistre# 1458) (Folder Portfolio 6D)
  - [Armor] (JHH# 132 / Enregistre# 1459) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    Artist: J. Dumont Printmaker: Blondel Publisher: Huquier
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 166 / Enregistre# 1460) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    18th Century French Engraving
    Artist: Huret Printmaker: Rousselet Publisher: Mariette
  - Ambassades envoyees des extremites de la Terre (JHH# 171 / Enregistre# 1461) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    17th Century French Engraving, etching
    Artist: Charles Le Brun Printmaker: Soubeuran Publisher:
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 185 / Enregistre# 1462) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    17th Century French Etching, engraving
    Artist: N. Bertin Printmaker: L. Desplaces Publisher: Beauvais
  - Amerique (JHH# 328 / Enregistre# 1463) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: N. Guerard
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1343 / Enregistre# 1464) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - Africa (JHH# 1684 / Enregistre# 1465) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    17th Century Italian Engraving
    Artist: Gio. Antonio Ricci Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Africa (JHH# 1722 / Enregistre# 1466) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    17th Century Dutch Engraving, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Peter Schenck
  - America (JHH# 1723 / Enregistre# 1467) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - America (JHH# 2009 / Enregistre# 1468) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Trouvain
  - America (JHH# 6442 / Enregistre# 1469) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    18th Century German Engraving
    Artist: Martin Engelbrecht Printmaker: Publisher:
  - L'Europe (JHH# 6463 / Enregistre# 1471) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    17th Century French Engraving
    Artist: N. Bertin Printmaker: Desplaces Publisher: Desplaces
  - L'Europe (JHH# 7205 / Enregistre# 1472) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 7206 / Enregistre# 1473) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 7207 / Enregistre# 1474) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 7208 / Enregistre# 1475) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - Sibylla Europaea (JHH# 7631 / Enregistre# 1476) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - Sibylla Erythraea (JHH# 7632 / Enregistre# 1477) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
  - Plafond du Grand Escalier du Chateau de Versailles (JHH# 168 / Enregistre# 1478) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    Artist: Charles Le Brun Printmaker: C. Simonneau Publisher: Surugue
  - Vue interieure du Grand Escalier de Versailles (JHH# 170 / Enregistre# 1479) (Folder Portfolio 6E)
    Artist: Charles Le Brun Printmaker: J.M. Chevotet Publisher: Surugue
  - Tableau de principaux Peuples de L'Amerique (JHH# 159 / Enregistre# 1480) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    Artist: J.G. St. Sauveur Printmaker: Mixelle Publisher: Bance
  - Les IV Parties du Monde (JHH# 341 / Enregistre# 1481) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - Africa (JHH# 2077 / Enregistre# 1482), 1795 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    18th Century English Stipple engraving
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: C. Taylor
  - Asia (JHH# 2078 / Enregistre# 1483), 1795 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - Europe (JHH# 2079 / Enregistre# 1484), 1795 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - America (JHH# 2080 / Enregistre# 1485), 1795 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Europe Asia Africa America] (JHH# 2152 / Enregistre# 1486), 1830 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    Artist: Richardson? Printmaker: Publisher: J. Harris
  - Tableaux des principaux Peuples de l'Asie (JHH# 2314 / Enregistre# 1487) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    Artist: J. G. St. Sauveur Printmaker: Malbest Publisher:
  - Tableaux des principaux Peuples de l'Europe (JHH# 2315 / Enregistre# 1488) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - Tableaux des principaux Peuples de l'Afrique (JHH# 2454 / Enregistre# 1489) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Amerique] (JHH# 5033 / Enregistre# 1490) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - La Fontaine des quatres Parties du Monde (JHH# 5900 / Enregistre# 1491), 1796 (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    Artist: F. de Cuvillies Printmaker: Joh. Nepo. Maag Publisher:
  - Aux Quatre Parties du Monde (JHH# 7110 / Enregistre# 1492) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
    18th Century French Etching, engraving
    Artist: Printmaker: Meunier Publisher:
  - [Right side of an Arch] (JHH# 7209 / Enregistre# 1493) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Right side of an Arch] (JHH# 7210 / Enregistre# 1494) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Left side of an Arch] (JHH# 7211 / Enregistre# 1495) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Left side of an Arch] (JHH# 7212 / Enregistre# 1496) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [Right side of an Arch] (JHH# 7213 / Enregistre# 1497) (Folder Portfolio 6F)
  - [America] (JHH# 129 / Enregistre# 1498) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - Cesse de t'affliger, o France (JHH# 339 / Enregistre# 1499), 1720 (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    Artist: B. Picart Printmaker: B. Picart Publisher: H. P. de Limiers
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1681 / Enregistre# 1500) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1682 / Enregistre# 1501) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1683 / Enregistre# 1502) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - America (JHH# 3124 / Enregistre# 1503) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - America (JHH# 3433 / Enregistre# 1504) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    Artist: F.P. Printmaker: Publisher:
  - L'Amour Europeen (JHH# 3945 / Enregistre# 1505) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    18th Century French Engraving, etching
    Artist: Chas. Eisen Printmaker: F. Basan Publisher: Basan
  - L'Amour Asiatique (JHH# 3946 / Enregistre# 1506) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - [Asia] (JHH# 4173 / Enregistre# 1507) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    18th Century French Stipple engraving, hand coloring
  - [Africa] (JHH# 4174 / Enregistre# 1508) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - Elle saisit l'instant (JHH# 4704 / Enregistre# 1509) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    Artist: A. Desenne Printmaker: Leroux Publisher:
  - O chere moitie de mon ame! (JHH# 4705 / Enregistre# 1510) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - Histoire des Avanturiers des Boucaniers (JHH# 7126 / Enregistre# 1511), 1743 (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - Les Voyages de Mr. De Thevenot (JHH# 7127 / Enregistre# 1512), 1743 (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - l'Asie (JHH# 7214 / Enregistre# 1513) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
    Artist: Jean Chas. Delafosse Printmaker: Jean Charles Delafosse Publisher:
  - l'Amerique (JHH# 7215 / Enregistre# 1514) (Folder Portfolio 6G)
  - Plan d'un Edifice Consacre a la Paix (JHH# 7226 / Enregistre# 1515) (Folder 6H)
    Artist: Le Boursier Printmaker: Pierre-Claude de la Gardette Publisher: Pierre-Claude de la Gardette
- Series IX: Allegorical, Spanish and Portuegese
  - Le Nouveau Monde affranchi (JHH# 1677 / Enregistre# 1516) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    18th Century French Etching and stipple
  - Europa (JHH# 2197 / Enregistre# 1517) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    18th Century Spanish Engraving, etching
    Artist: Luca Giordano Printmaker: J. Barcelon Publisher: J. Castillo
  - Asia (JHH# 2198 / Enregistre# 1518) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    Artist: Luca Giordano Printmaker: Nicolas Bassanti Publisher: J. Castillo
  - Africa (JHH# 2199 / Enregistre# 1519) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    Artist: Luca Giordano Printmaker: Juan Barcelon Publisher: J. Castillo
  - America (JHH# 2200 / Enregistre# 1520) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
  - Europa (JHH# 2201 / Enregistre# 1521) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    Artist: Luca Giordano Printmaker: Juan Antonio Salvador Carmona Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 2202 / Enregistre# 1522) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
  - Africa (JHH# 2203 / Enregistre# 1523) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
  - America (JHH# 2204 / Enregistre# 1524) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
  - Lamina de la Mascara Real (JHH# 2210 / Enregistre# 1525) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    18th Century Spanish Etching
    Artist: Franciscus Tramullas Printmaker: Defehrt Publisher:
  - Segundo Alvarez (JHH# 3682 / Enregistre# 1526) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    19th Century Spanish Reproductive print
  - Coleccion Universal (JHH# 4221 / Enregistre# 1527) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
  - Espana e Indias Reuni (JHH# 5213 / Enregistre# 1528) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    19th Century Spanish Etching
  - Theatre de L'univers (JHH# 6419 / Enregistre# 1529), 1581 (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    16th Century French Engraving, etching
    Artist: Abraham Ortelius Printmaker: Publisher: Abraham Ortelius
  - America Europa Asia Africa (JHH# 7501 / Enregistre# 1530) (Folder Portfolio 6i)
    17th? Century French Etching, engraving
- Series X: Allegorical, Italian
  - Nave di Amerigo Vespucci Intermedio Quarto (JHH# 2167 / Enregistre# 1531), 1608 (Folder Portfolio 7A)
    Artist: Giulio Parigi Printmaker: Remigio Cantagallina Publisher:
  - Lettere in Vari Generi (JHH# 3431 / Enregistre# 1532), 1641 (Folder Portfolio 7A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Amadore Massi
  - Venient annis Saecula seris (JHH# 6418 / Enregistre# 1533) (Folder Portfolio 7A)
    Artist: Carlo Coltellini Printmaker: F. Gregory Publisher:
  - L'America (JHH# 307 / Enregistre# 1534) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    18th Century Italian Aquatint, etching, hand coloring
    Artist: Appiani Printmaker: Fumagalli Publisher:
  - America (JHH# 329 / Enregistre# 1535) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    18th Century Italian Etching, roulette
    Artist: Amiconi Printmaker: Joh. Christoph Publisher:
  - Europa (JHH# 908 / Enregistre# 1536), 1791 (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    Artist: Ap. Theodorum Viero Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 909 / Enregistre# 1537), 1791 (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - Africa (JHH# 910 / Enregistre# 1538), 1791 (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - America (JHH# 911 / Enregistre# 1539), 1791 (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - L'Africa (JHH# 1856 / Enregistre# 1540) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    19th Century Italian Lithograph, hand coloring
    Artist: Carlo Verdoni Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Madrigale (JHH# 2274 / Enregistre# 1541) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - Europe (JHH# 3108 / Enregistre# 1542) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    18th Century Italian Etching, hand coloring
    Artist: Amiconi Printmaker: G. Wagner Publisher: Carington Bowles
  - Asia (JHH# 3109 / Enregistre# 1543) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - Europa (JHH# 3163 / Enregistre# 1544) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
    Artist: Remondini? Printmaker: Publisher: Bassano
  - Asia (JHH# 3164 / Enregistre# 1545) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - Africa (JHH# 3165 / Enregistre# 1546) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - America (JHH# 3166 / Enregistre# 1547) (Folder Portfolio 7B)
  - Europa (JHH# 3203 / Enregistre# 1548) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    Artist: Amiconi Printmaker: Jean Renard Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 3204 / Enregistre# 1549) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - Affrica [sic] (JHH# 3205 / Enregistre# 1550) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - America (JHH# 3206 / Enregistre# 1551) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - Prospettiva della Prima Macchina de Fuochi (JHH# 4734 / Enregistre# 1552), 1749 (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Michele Sorello Publisher: Francesco Scardovelli
  - Europa/ Asia (JHH# 4796 / Enregistre# 1553a), 1816 (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    19th Century Italian Etching, hand coloring
    Artist: A. Appiani Printmaker: Antonio Rancati Publisher:
  - Duettino (JHH# 4901 / Enregistre# 1554) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    18th Century Italian Engraving
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Gio. Chiari
  - L'Europa (JHH# 5462 / Enregistre# 1555) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - L'America (JHH# 5463 / Enregistre# 1556) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - Asia (JHH# 7633 / Enregistre# 1557) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    Artist: Ferrario Printmaker: Domenico Cagnoni Publisher:
  - Africa (JHH# 7634 / Enregistre# 1558) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
  - America (JHH# 7647 / Enregistre# 1559) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
    Artist: Sansever Printmaker: Dall'Acqua Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 912 / Enregistre# 1560) (Folder Portfolio 7C)
- Series XI: Allegorical, English
  - Europe (JHH# 1112 / Enregistre# 1561) (Folder Portfolio 8)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: C. Dicey
  - Asia (JHH# 1113 / Enregistre# 1562) (Folder Portfolio 8)
  - Africa (JHH# 1114 / Enregistre# 1563) (Folder Portfolio 8)
  - America (JHH# 1115 / Enregistre# 1564) (Folder Portfolio 8)
  - St. George (JHH# 3113 / Enregistre# 1565), 1794 (Folder Portfolio 8)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Laurie and Whittle
  - [Commemorative print for Capt Sir. P.B.V. Broke] (JHH# 4213 / Enregistre# 1566), 1816 (Folder Portfolio 8)
    19th Century English Etching, aquatint
    Artist: Printmaker: Henry Meyer Publisher: S. Hougham
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1353 / Enregistre# 1567) (Folder Portfolio 8)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Marotte
- Series XII: Religious, French
  - [Assumption of the Virgin] (JHH# 1580 / Enregistre# 1568) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Jos. Olivieri Printmaker: Giovanni Petrini Publisher:
  - Historia (JHH# 1652 / Enregistre# 1569) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    17th Century Dutch Etching, engraving
    Artist: Ioan. Miele Printmaker: C. Bloemaert Publisher:
  - La Sangre Preciosisima de Jesucristo (JHH# 2548 / Enregistre# 1570), 1884 (Folder Portfolio 9)
    19th Century Spanish Lithograph
    Artist: J. Morell Printmaker: Publisher:
  - La Sangre Preciosisima de Jesucristo (JHH# 2543 / Enregistre# 1571) (Folder Portfolio 9)
  - La Sangre Preciosisima de Jesucristo (JHH# 2544 / Enregistre# 1572) (Folder Portfolio 9)
  - S. Joannes Baptista de la Salle (JHH# 2546 / Enregistre# 1573) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    19th Century French Reproductive prints
    Artist: Gagliardi Printmaker: Publisher: A. Marini
  - St. Francois-Xavier (JHH# 10001 / Enregistre# 1574) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    19th Century French Woodcut, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Epinal
  - Monument Simbolique et historique (JHH# 3286 / Enregistre# 1575) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Berauld
  - Sanctificetur Nomen tuum (JHH# 3688 / Enregistre# 1576) (Folder Portfolio 9)
  - [Religious sculpture] (JHH# 4736 / Enregistre# 1577) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Ioan. Giarni Printmaker: Ioan. Giarni Publisher: M. Joseph Limpach
  - [Sculpture with Europe, Asia, Africa] (JHH# 4738 / Enregistre# 1578) (Folder Portfolio 9)
  - Reloj de la Sagrada Pasion de Cristo (JHH# 4746 / Enregistre# 1579) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Printmaker: Melchor Guasp Publisher:
  - Gozos a la Preciosisima Sangre de Jesucristo (JHH# 4747 / Enregistre# 1580) (Folder Portfolio 9)
  - Orbis-Catholici-Romae (JHH# 5452 / Enregistre# 1581), 1893 (Folder Portfolio 9)
    19th Century Italian Reproductive print
    Artist: Virginio Monti Printmaker: P. Miani Publisher: C. Virano e Ci.
  - COR Iesu Honoratum (JHH# 5616 / Enregistre# 1582) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    18th Century German Etching, engraving
    Artist: Printmaker: Catharina Klauber Publisher: Catharina Klauber
  - S. Maria (JHH# 5960 / Enregistre# 1583) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Franz Endress Printmaker: Franz Endress Publisher:
  - Gratia Semen Dei (JHH# 5961 / Enregistre# 1584) (Folder Portfolio 9)
    Artist: Printmaker: I.A. Pfeffel Publisher:
  - Agnus Dei Qui Tollis Peccata Mundi (JHH# 5962 / Enregistre# 1585) (Folder Portfolio 9)